

# **PROFILE**

I'm Lukas, a self-taught software developer currently studying M.Sc. Engineering Physics at Lund University. Driven by curiosity, I constantly seek new things to learn like philosophy, math, politics, or programming. I've more than one year of experience as a full-time developer, but many more as a hobbyist.

If a picture can say more than a thousand words, a website can say more than a thousand resumés. With that I want to say that you should check out my website for a more complete picture of me. Visit: https://lukaspetersson.se/

### CONTACT

PHONE:

+46 707898860

EMAIL:

Lukas.Petersson.1999@gmail.com

GITHUB:

https://github.com/lukaspetersson

### **ANDROID APPS**

- BookLog
- Falling Kitten
- Brännbollräknare

#### **OTHER**

- Lund Startup Fellowship fellow
- FARAD (job fair) IT-manager
- Martial art studies in China
- Liberal youth party active member
- Football player for 15 years
- Science competition semi-finalist
- Erasmus+ symposium 2017 in Genoa
- Driver's license
- Loves running

# LUKAS PETERSSON

# Student and Software developer

#### **EDUCATION**

M.Sc. Engineering Physics, Lund University

2019 - 2024

GPA: 4.0/4 (Swedish equivalent: 5.0/5)

Natural Science, Kungsholmens gymnasium

2015 - 2018

GPA: 3.92/4 (Swedish equivalent: 22.1/22.5)

# **RELEVANT WORK EXPERIENCE**

IT-Consultant, Lunicore

Nov 2019 – Present, Part time

Full Stack development for different clients. I am working with many different APIs since no two projects are alike.

#### Software developer, Digital Edge

Nov 2018 – Jul 2019, Full time (weekends during Ericsson internship) Programming a robot to work as a receptionist using Vue.js for the frontend and Python for communication with the robot's limbs.

#### Software developer intern, Ericsson

Jan 2019 – May 2019, Full time

I made web applications using React.js and Android apps using Kotlin. Working at a huge company taught me how organizations of different sizes operates.

#### OTHER WORK EXPERIENCES

Substitute teacher Engelska skolan Oct - Nov 2018 Oct - Nov 2018 Sales Assistant Hemköp Entertainer TUI Summer 2018 Waiter Bedinge GK Summer 2017 Golf coach Drottningholms GK 2015 - 2017 Dishwasher Summer 2015 & 2016

Abbekås hamnkrog

#### PROGRAMMING SKILLS

